William Bratz

Full Stack Developer

CONTACT INFO

ADDRESS

107 Connie Drive Hendersonville TN, 37075

PHONE

(615) 210-9939

FMAII

WilliamBratz615@gmail.com

APPLICABLE SKILLS

C#/.NET

* * * * *

React JS

* * * *

Docker

* * * *

TeamCity ★★★★

Octopus Deploy

* * * *

Azure DevOps

* * * *

Kubernetes

* * * *

Azure

* * * *

AWS

* * * *

SQL Server

Javascript

нтмі

++++

^ ^ ^ ^ ^

++++

CSS

PROFILE

Hello! I am William Bratz, but everyone calls me Billy. I am a full stack developer with extensive experience in developing enterprise full stack web applications, microservice architecture, and cloud development using Azure, and AWS.

I am comfortable in any environment, but thrive in fast paced surroundings with projects that require me to learn and grow my skills. Learning and improving are more than goals of mine, they are passions.

Thank you and I look forward to working with you soon!

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Carvana

Software Engineer II

2020 - Present

At Carvana, I work with microservices deployed to Azure service fabric and kubernetes. One of my primary responsibilities is to migrate these microservices from service fabric to kubernetes. Some of my other responsibilities include:

- Develop, and deploy scalable microservices that receive over 100,000 requests an hour.
- · Utilize splunk to troubleshoot/monitor services.
- · RESTful API development using .net core.
- · Maintaining unit test coverage using nUnit/xUnit.
- · Conversion of .net framework applications to .net core.
- · Continuous Delivery (CD) using Azure DevOps
- · Review pull requests for teammates.

STE

Software Engineer II (Full Stack)

2015 - 2020

At STR my primary role was to architect and develop web applications utilizing Javascript (React, Typescript), C# (.NET Core), and SQL Server or DynamoDB. Outside of my main job I also took on additional responsibilities such as:

- · Team Lead for "Instant Insights Project".
- · Developing cloud applications using AWS Lambda, Step Functions, and DynamoDb.
- Hosting multiple Lunch and learns for the development organization.
- Taking part in multiple company development groups tasked with researching and improving company implementation of technology area (Architecture, C#, Front end).
- I also obtained multiple company awards for outstanding performance.

EDUCATION

Associates Degree in Applied Science, Computer Programming, Volunteer State

2021 - 2022

2021 Dean's List

University transfer program Bachelors Degree in computer science, AB Tech Community College

2009 - 201

OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTIONS

RestSharp

NUnit

PERSONAL PROJECTS

William Bratz dot com, Github repo

Personal website to test out languages, coding paradigms, and general technology related fun. Uses Next JS, React, deployed to Heroku with CD.

Sunny's Light, SunnysLight.org

501(c)(3) Non-profit founded by my wife and I following the stillbirth of our daughter Sunny.

Uses React, .NET Core 3.1 Api. Azure SQL Server database. Custom stripe integration, Azure App Services, front end is containerized using docker. CD using Azure DevOps.